My master...safe.
The scriptures...sound.
All I ever wanted was a life in my mountain, free from you and your so-called merits.
Those high above don't trust me. I understand that.
And they send you and those knuckleheads to threaten me.
To obey and serve once more.
I understand that too.
But what I don't understand is...
You bastards killing my kind!
Stay back, stupid dog.
Stay back,uurgh
Stay back,supid dog!
Savor it.
no
Feck this screen!
Savorti.
Savorty, they won't respond any more!
Savor them on the grid!
Mark this!
Mark This!
Mark It!
Mark This.
He's not just any monkey.
He's a monkey of merit.
A monkey was made Buddha once.
None other than me can challenge him to a duel.
Look, monkey.
I don't make a habit of fighting someone I've bested before.
Here's my offer.
If you lose, I'll take you to the Celestial Court.
They will stay and level your mountain.
But if I lose, I shall certainly take revenge.
And they will level your mountain nonetheless.
How tragic would that be, huh?
You are one of the court.
We don't need to resort to violence.
How about you bend the knees, admit the wrongs, and we can put this behind us?
All these years...
Except for that pig.
You're the one who talks the tallest tales.
Good. I am entertained.
Speaking of entertainment...
Wouldn't it be fun if I pluck your extra eye out for my snack
and allow you to keep the other two?
Because I'd hate to let you miss how I'll slaughter each mongrel of the court.
Those below, those above, and that black mutt of yours.
Come at me.
All of you!