Oi kid, you look suspicious. What kind of yaoguai are you?
I'm looking at that Buddha over there
See his belly button. It's so big
Me and you we look way smaller. Buddha?
Where is it?
You see no Buddha because you think no Buddha
No thought no sight
I, the sacred Gourmand, saw enough Buddhas before you were born
Foolish brat
You didn't see that coming did you?
True hearts find their path and the Buddha is on that path
Why not worship with a true heart? The path might just show itself
Worship my hoof! Visit temples, kneel to figures, you tell no black from white. That's my master.
I am fed up with all these skin-deep rites
No true heart, the path is sealed
With true heart it's revealed