You cunning wretch! I'll spare your sorry life for today!
Fortune is no longer on your side!
No one will come to your aid. All I need is to take it elsewhere and rebuild everything anew!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Great... sage!
Oh, pardon me, young sage! Mercy!
I was just a pawn of the Celestial Court!
If given a choice, who dared to challenge the mighty wrecker of the Celestial Palace?
His words ring true. No matter how daring he was, he had not the nerve to harm the great sage.
There must be someone else pulling all the strings.
Exactly!
I'm sorry, young sage. I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
Exactly! And this thing is eerie! I had no idea how to make use of its power...
...except to enshrine it up there, tricking lesser yaoguays into offerings!
If you pardon me, I'll go back to Guan Yin to atone for my actions and be put back on the engaging band!
You will never see me out there anymore!
Oh, ignore his nonsense! Go now, little monkey! Go and retrieve the great sage's relic!
MRS JUNG!
I can't hear you!
What?
Mwee!
You have not heard my懂ings?
Tell me about your memory.
How did Mwee old man come to know you?
Of course I heard him.
Don't take that from me!
How could you, young sage?
Strange, young sage, think so?
Maybehe has known each other for many years, but after what happened, he hid a little secret in his heart.
He was just like a clam to disown his muzzle everyone.
Is that right?
You did not like him?
No.