You're here.
We're here.
Step aboard.
Hey, old monkey.
I hope this isn't a one-way trip, is it?
Isn't all life a one-way trip?
Once you embark on the journey, there's no turning back.
What is this place?
His memories.
Since his early days, he'd had an eye for the finer things, and a will to wrest them from others.
Laying his eyes on, then craving to see.
His memories.
Their riches.
No better than the Black Bear and Jincha, I say.
He can't have an eye for the finer things, while the Buddha oversees the three realms?
Well, I hardly think that's fair.
How insatiable.
Not content with his kingdom and title below, he asked for a position in the Celestial Court.
But soon after his wish was granted,
his joy turned to rage.
All because he wasn't invited to a feast.
He nearly ruined the entire Celestial Palace.
Ah, years fume at unfavorable news.
As untamed and ungrateful as that yellow rat.
Beasts are beasts, don't you think?
He was young. He didn't know any better.
Hadn't learned from the Buddha or our master yet.
But he was young. He didn't know any better. Hadn't learned from the Buddha or our master yet.
But he was young. He didn't know any better.
Aren't you being a bit harsh? Dredging up the scandals from his youth?
Like his adulthood was any better.
Since his release, he had claimed to have learned manners and discipline.
Yet his wee frankincense gave him away.
Posing as an idol, he degraded the gods.
Clear was his defiance of the doctrines he had learned.
Well, he was so much more than that.
He was just being naughty.
Aren't all great achievers somewhat self-obsessed?
Myself included.
Nose in the air, feeling above others.
I say, he was no less insolent than that yellow-browed brat.
Wait, isn't it that... the lady of some sort?
Hmm.
It was her tricks that made Master drive Wukong away.
On White Tiger Ridge, he forsook his love.
Three times he broke her into pieces, convincing himself his heart would ache no more.
Yet, as you must know, he had never let go of her.
Otherwise,
he wouldn't have been so eager to get away from the Buddha-hood he attained.
Those who talk much of love will one day bite their tongues.
On this matter, he was akin to you and your many darlings.
No matter where you are, you'd always fall captive to the web of mortal desire.
Why bring me into this?
True, I don't have the wits to break the web, but...
He had torn his way out since that day.
Gah.
Take a look, Bajie. Can you see?
Many of your good friends are here.
We're just fair-weather friends, that's all.
But they are still friends, aren't they?
So you say, so it must be.
These old buddies...
I think none of them ended up well.
Indeed.
For ages, countless gifted souls have walked this earth.
Yet of them, how few have forged everlasting greatness.
Do you know why?
Injustice?
Never has it been just.
Misfortune?
Fortune is simply...
Humility in the mighty.
Well, mayhaps.
They simply lacked my charm.
Gifted they may be, yet strive they not.
Content with little, and lost in lust.
Seek the ease, yet crave the renown.
They yearn for freedom, yet aspire to Buddhahood.
They always want both.
Yet nobody can, and nobody should.
Such was the folly of the Bull King and Wukong.
I'm sorry, but I'm sorry.
Destiny's favor calls for the resolution to sever all desires.
You should mark well these words.
I'm sorry, but I'm sorry.
Hold on.
This can't be Wukong's memory.
You're fooling us, aren't you?
Ah.
Five of the six relics call for one.
Bajie, tell me which.
Eye, ear, nose, tongue, body, and mind.
Mind!
It's mind.
What did you just see?
The three of us?
That was the last one.
Oh, I see now.
It was you.
I knew it from the beginning.
You were the mind of Wukong all along.
That's why you led us here.
Not me.
It's him.
Don't make me laugh.
Him?
He is Wukong?
Yes...
and no.
Cuts to the chase, will you?
We didn't come this far for your riddles.
After Wukong died,
five of his six senses endured
and were taken by the Yaoguai kings.
Only his mind was lost.
Mind is the first of the six.
It's the essence unique to every life.
Therefore,
its destiny
is to fade away at life's end.
Hold on.
You mean Wukong's gone for good?
Never to return?
You old bastard!
You've been lying to us all this time!
That Wukong you knew will never return.
But what made him remains.
The universe will always bear him a successor.
One who shall carry on his name and nature.
This chosen successor is the destined one.
Nameless you were.
Yet perils and mighty foes you've braved to recover his relics.
Your will now stands resolute, worthy of his power.
You mean this is the end of the world?
You mean this boy is to take Wukong's name?
He's not!
Soon Wukong is long gone!
Bajie, Deep Town, you know he wasn't all that perfect.
Now that he is dead, this one, perhaps, shall bear the name in his stead.