Help! Help me, young master!
It's you, kind monkey! Help me! Help me, please!
Things went south in the mountain and I barely escaped.
But on my way down, Gwai's captured me.
I've been kept here for three days.
But now my luck has returned.
My savior appeared here right in front of me.
Should you extend your mercy to save my family?
I'll repay your kindness at any cost.
Master got it right.
The last surely knows how to ask for help.
It's them.
My captors are back. Please don't leave me.
Easy catch.
And what now?
Burn them all to cinders!
Ha ha ha! Burn them! Burn them!
Keep em safe.
It's too late now.
Okay, it's over.
They stood up to command the forces on the Englishная warrior центр.
Must have been the muốnir of those components.
No, they must be being pushed onto byinäainaā in return.
A man must five times have to keep them in place.
And that's really what happened!
Oh, yes.