Please, you must save me.
So, both my trap and my vessel failed. But how?
When I saw him, I just couldn't. The destined one then arrived and bested me. Now the monkey has ransacked our hollow.
A mere monkey showing such disrespect. Your wound was recovering. But now it's getting worse. Fear not, I'll deal with him.
But before that, that thing of mine, do you still have it?
I do.
Very well. Despite all your failures, you led the destined one here. I should reward you for that.
But the thing I gave you, now I must have it back!
I must get back!
Ash mountains are still poisonous.
Hoc ell de Oasis
You girls are far too young, to comprehend my tears.
O Rapids, but why?
design. This, along with those relics inside him, shall free me of Kunlun's reign. Rest
assured, darling, I'll avenge you. Now let go of your misery and rest in peace.
you