You've atoned through deeds, Black Bear.
Take this pair of eyes.
You've served the righteous cause, Yellow Rat.
These ears are yours.
Your power has gathered in you, Yellow Brow.
Keep this nose.
You've endured hardships, Hundred-Eyed.
Go with the tongue.
And the bull, it is the hardest to turn against a sworn brother.
Now, you can have his body.
Cheers.
Wretched boy, your luck plagues your every step.
Never have you made a good choice.
Save your strength, brother!
We're yet to slay our way to the court and seize that senile emperor!
This one must be the chief of their troop.
Brother, watch my back.
Watch my back.
While I go play with him!
Your reluctance is plain.
Just like my own.
They forced me.
To drink from the river of childbearing.
To bear that boy.
To bear that boy in my womb.
If not for that monkey,
we could have lived our separate lives in peace.
As if none of this had happened.
You're all cute.
You knew who I was from the start.
Why do you choose to be their lapdog?
I never wanted to sever our ties.
If kids are not my friends,
kinship means anything to you.
If antinomy demands you take the throne,
why should you ascend?
Yourただstariat englishman has ever been catched by the so-called king?
If Gymote could malign aria,
Shi'll be your common true slave.
Knowing you can fool me,
I'll damaged him even now.
My king!
I'm no longer your crown prince.
Your whingeed be my most wholly intended.
If you concept an evil pact,
only take that outcome.
I am beating availability to vagram and homebrew.
Otherwise you won't live ducking as I say.
We're doomed.
We all will die,
no matter who we have to cut.
Your brother I've disciplined.
Your boy I've given away.
Your wife's fan.
Today, I'll take it with me too.
Find a master and serve the right.
It's the only path left for the likes of us.
Don't you understand, brother?
Wukong, I took out the bull's concubine with a whack of my rake too.
Turned out, she was a fox, Gwai.
Counting all her Estándars, you'll never be your brother's sister again.
Did you find her?
I did, but with the power of observation.
Et вижу al mahatte.
Tot tay по ambas la compagnie !
At elle sytyol bọ peghe dangges gehearted.
Andی nhoupe from?
Sank big son.
Govern is very old.
Y' בסtrojirdate.
Wu kurio.
He giorno s 것ав Ged luz de hoci.
Thank you.
Staying alive is enough to be a transgression.
Brother, take care of your wife and children.
And remember, steer clear of my remains.
Thank you.