Father, I've brought him here. It's the destined one. Brother is not around. You can hand it over to him now.
Brother will surely give up on his plan once it's returned. And then we will be a family again.
You mischievous monkey. You dare to push your luck, but always have a way out.
Only you came back at the wrong time.
Are you not thinking straight, Father? I brought the destined one here to save you.
I may be unwell, but I am not blind. You are not my daughter.
How can you say that to me? I went through flames to find the destined one for you. For you, Father, don't you see?
I should have locked my eyes out too.
To save you.
To save me from your pretense.
Worry not, old horned fool. I'll see to it shortly.
You could have enjoyed a good show.
But you simply lost.
You simply lost.
You lack the taste. I should have just killed you all.
My guise was perfect. None could see a single flaw in it. How did you find out then?
Unlike you, she has never needed to fake her respect for me.
Interesting.
It's that little fox.
I will find out if it's true after I hunt her down.
But first, I should burn you two together and mix your ashes to honor your friendship.
Entertainment.
That can wait.