Foolhardy. Nothing more. I've done as our brother asked. Till we meet again!
I'm sorry, I can't help you.
No, I'm not sorry.
It's okay.
Your faith has led you here.
Rest easy.
You won't find those noisy chanting.
and pained screamings here.
A nice ripe melon.
Want a bite?
Mmm.
It's better than you think.
Sun Wukong used it to trick that disciple of mine.
Come.
Come closer.
Now you've found this place, I'll teach you a trick neither of them knows.
Your hand.
Spellbinder. It hurts no foe but binds yourself.
You'll come to understand its use.
An old friend of Sun Wukong came to me, wanting some peace.
I led him to the Great Pagoda. Have you paid him a visit?
They say you are the destined one.
But if destiny is set, what difference do our actions make?
This is the greatest adventure of all.
Sun Wukong and Sun Wukong.
Fade away.
Just like the sun.
And then, the sun will not shine.
The sun will not shine.
Sun Wukong.