Here, we can venture forth with you no further.
This task is yours alone.
Sun Wukong left behind a broken shell, stripped of all his six senses.
Though ages have passed, it maintains a connection attuned to the echoes of his former self.
If you truly are the one destined, you must cast aside his soulless shell and merge the
six into one.
Then, you shall be the one to begin the journey anew.
No!
Not on his own!
He's just a kid who knows nothing!
I'll go with him!
This place is shaped by Wukong's lingering obsession.
It allows only his own self.
It allows only his relic-bearer to face the final ordeal.
We can escort him no more.
See it for yourself.
Hear me, Sun!
You can always run!
You don't have to bear Wukong's name!
...