you
You
Admiral why so stubborn keep at it you could melt into blood and pus
Darling come on. It's perfectly cool in here
Join me inside for some yin yang practice with you
such humor
Admiral let go of your stubbornness and I could request master to set you free
Then I'd be open to joining you
Even you celestial courtier bend to his will
Yet my ears tell me that the destined one has stopped the money will
Pity reckon it won't be your master who unlocks these metals eventually
These gold symbols are made by our Grand Master
And you think a puny monkey can go beyond that?
Yeah
You
You've roused turtle general. How could you know he's here below?
Turtle snake who cares I caught a whiff of monkey stench familiar enough for me to sound by welcome
Master values
Master values your talent he kept you alive beneath the pagoda for your own good
Master values your talents he kept you alive beneath the pagoda for your own good
How ungrateful evidently you just don't deserve the ecstasy of the new west
Stay watching for the next episode of winter