You cursed monkey.
Wherever you go,
you leave behind a ruined family.
My son is defeated,
but not vanquished.
I am afraid he'll rise again soon.
Since it came into my possession,
I've kept it in my stomach.
Hidden from all.
I am old now.
Fears have grown in me.
Fear of war.
Fear of death.
Fear of my wife.
Fear of my son.
That is why I dare not consume it,
let alone give it back to him.
I am destined, deprived.
It's all the same.
Don't ever believe their bullshit.
You are your choices,
your causes and effects,
not what you're called.
First bring Fire Emblem into this world.
I 세상 방 Jake Sea and my body.
Austin-kan
Faster.
해를 tus아렴.
N bate marina
You
No wonder not a single raindrop was fanned it was your trick the whole time
My bad old bull I was a bit delayed
You little rascal. I'll teach you a lesson on your parents behalf