Keep this cicada safe with you. It'll come in handy.
Enough about your brother. If you care for him so much, why not go back to him and give me some peace?
If you won't act, Mother, then I implore you to lend me your plantain fan to save Father.
Save him? Or this mountain from its doom? Both are beyond this fan.
Mother, please. I am begging you. Father's life hangs on a thread. A thread which Brother could cut short any moment.
Since when did you start caring for that old bull?
Do not think you can hide your secret wish from me.
You wish you could rule this mountain with your brother once we are finished.
If you won't act, Mother, then I implore you to lend me your plantain fan to save Father.
If you want to save Father, then I will.
You are a cunning fox. You just want to trade my fan for a smile on your brother's face.
I owe my life to Father. And to your kindness for taking me in.
Brother was good to me, but I would never betray my parents for him.
Say no more of the fact that you love Father.
I am a good man. We raised the boy. Guess this is what we deserve.
But you... Why are you here at this very moment?
Rakshasi, I am not a part of your family. And I am aware I have no voice in this.
But Ping told me the destined one had arrived.
Hmph. The destined one? Who doesn't even know what he's destined for?
Those old bastards must have pulled a muscle coming up with the name.
You and I both know who he truly is.
When the time comes, your children, your husband, and even this very palace...
...could all turn to ashes.
What do I have to fear from a mere pawn?
He's no match for us.
You can't even rival the power of my fan.
Once the truth is revealed, suddenly he is here.
Do you not find it odd? Such a twist of fate.
The truth? The truth of what? Who are you talking about?
I heard the Destined One had obtained all the other relics.
Rakshasi, your situation is grave.
Do you not see who mandated his return?
Were those relics really bestowed for your good?
Perhaps amid these schemes and plots,
we've unwittingly become stepping stones for his rebirth.
For others, I care not.
All along, you are all I care for.
I say we should leave together.
I vow to treasure you dearly, just like when we were up there.
I never thought that one day you'd be the only one I can rely on.
I am overwhelmed.
Come, sit with me, and tell me what to do.
Don't let him, Mother!
Don't you see? He is taking advantage of you!
You! You ledger!
Not for your help! Not your treachery!
How dare you!
A child of a concubine should know better manners.
When I first crossed paths with her,
your bull of a father was no more than livestock munching on a patch of grass.
Have you no shame? Mother, don't be fooled!
Enough of your endless prattle.
No! No!
No!
No.
That's better.
Rakshasi, have we not been this close since our time in Tishita Palace?
Well, yes.
I do miss the old days, too.
We were so happy back then.
What's in the blazes?
No jigs here.
It's just my hood.
Oof! You deserve to know before we kiss.
You will live to repent this!
Filthy lowlife!
You dare take her form and beguile me?
My old friend, wasn't it fun?
Have we not been this close since our carnage in the fox den?
You abhorrent fraud!
My candid words were wasted on your foul ears!
Candid, my hoof!
Your revenants are everywhere!
I thought you'd have better lies!