I saw how this would end for you long ago.
Keep fighting for others, and in time, you shall fall by their hands.
I, Yellowbrow, fight solely for myself.
I haven't lost.
I will not lose.
If only I could wield that monkey's rake just once more.
I must fight.
Hmm.
This Rogue stole my Seedsack and fled here.
With Wu Kong's Relic he made it a soul-snatching vessel.
He also took my Look, and my Name, to trick his old friends.
trick his old foes into vengeance.
You pot belly!
I should have figured out it was you.
Forgive my little deception.
Stolen once, I buy it.
Stolen twice, I doubt it.
Your doubt is fair.
I shouldn't have underestimated his nerve.
I meant to subdue him myself,
but you two were swifter.
Fortune favors you, Bajie.
But I see great potential in this young one.
He might just be...
the right monkey.
Enough of this empty talk!
I don't care if Yellowbrow drowns in the lake.
We can't have Wukong's relic sink with him!
For that, pray lend me that rake of yours.
Bajie!
가
is
this
and
we
are
not
together.
Hey!
You hurt 172!
He's evil!
you