My friend, we've stuck a gold with this task, haven't we?
Gold, my ass.
My bones are cracking from lugging this load.
Step it up.
I gotta catch that feast on time.
Hear me out.
They say that hag has her quirky ways.
Each season she'd wed a mate, then devour him.
Once our lady brought her a wedding gift.
A mirror.
The past echo.
Which?
The lady often speaks of it with regrets.
I wonder why.
Let me finish, will you?
The hag got the mirror and looked into it,
and for no reason at all, she threw it away.
That soured our lady's mood.
She stopped visiting since then.
Gibbering and jabbering.
Couldn't even catch her.
She was in a wink of sleep this whole time.
What? Who's in there?
How dare you spoil the gifts from Mount Wushan?
Grrrr!
You really thought I of what happened these days.
Hey! Lovely!
Why don't you come down and join us?
Leaving so soon?
Why, the shyness?!