You
Master paid this child be born but he never knew my struggles
How can we but follow the master's word
Raksha see you know it was he who made you drink from the river of childbearing
Shut it you shall never speak of it
The king knows why I had to drink it
But I haven't glimpsed him ever since then he made it another reason for his absence
Raksha see your husband shirks a dishonor this way
He granted you this cave with his mount bishwa beast as a sentinel. He's compromised enough for the sake of our master
You will seal your lips on this
Family would be doomed if anyone knew the truth behind this child
Fair not master bids me age you in secret
You and the bull
You will rear this child to manhood
When the boy comes of age
Well on that day
He will be living proof of the dark deeds of Mount Ling Shan
You