...
Quite the charmer, aren't you, boy?
But these eyes have seen prettier
disguises.
...
Your true face! Out with it!
If a single
lie slips, my rake shall
strike, too!
Hmph. That was
so close. Thank you for saving me.
I am the Bull King's daughter, Ping-Ping.
Nonsense!
The Bull has no daughter. Dare
to fool me, scoundrel?
I... I
know who you are!
My mother is Princess Fairfox.
You killed her!
...
After my mother died,
I've been living with my father.
His wife, Princess Rickshasi,
took me in as her own.
Later, brother came back
from Bodhisattva Guanyin, and we
reunited. We had some
peaceful days.
My brother was kind to me
and to our parents.
But somehow, not
long ago, he suddenly changed.
He secretly summoned his old
troops for a coup. Imprisoned father
kept mother under strict watch. I...
I had nowhere else to
return. I had to go for help.
...
But barely after leaving the place, his
minions fell upon me.
Heh. The Bull King's might is known.
Even together,
Wukong and I couldn't rival him.
Rickshasi's plantain fan
is also formidable. And you
want me to believe that they were subdued
by a kid?
... Subdued by
their son?
Who else could make them put
their guard down? Really, we're soft-hearted
and they could never harm him. You idiot!
This fox is fooling you!
Look at this place!
Only my brother's Samadhi fire
could wreak such havoc!
Oh no! My father
is dying! Please, kind monkey,
help me and my family!
A perilous place this is.
Keep this cicada
safe with you. It'll keep
coming handy.
...
That's a
voice I know well.
I'll go ahead and take a look.
...
No time to lose
now!
Follow me!
...
This way!
Keep up with me,
little ones!
...