Hold your monkeys.
Let me fix you up a little.
Welcome, good sirs. The feast is all set. Please come in and be our guests.
My, gentlemen. You're fashionably late.
Is your lady not joining us again this time?
Our lady prefers not to be late.
But she's been thinking of you all and sent this small token.
She hopes your lady will recover soon and pay her visit up there.
It's a pity she didn't come.
Or she would certainly enjoy a splendid show we've prepared for her.
But now...
The gift's gone and blood's been shed.
I say you two should take the fall.
We're just servants, madam.
What's the jest?
Zhu Ba Jie.
I know you find your look embarrassing.
But why hide from my mother with another pig face?
You rag Islamic Sh depending on a boner.
The time is now an best-待 thing.
We all know this little town is some ghoul shop.
This ten-year-old boy's usual poker face isn't important anymore, what devils!
Shut up, now!
Mistress Double's a single clueless woman, and Mr. 14th's like a fox in a sit-downey.
Thought this was an ending to the fish-free house?
Deserted, allied.
Blasphemous.
Tired.
Polite.
Reputation?
Yaoguai's care about reputation. All she cared about was lust.
Now I know. You're one of her spiderlings, aren't you?
Well, well. Your rudeness is forgiven. Show some respect. Maybe I'll kindly pay
your mother a visit.
Visit or not, I'm afraid that is not your call.