Behold! Be it the realm of sunset or the realm of gold, it's but an echo of the past.
Legends speak of an ancient, colossal beetle in these sands.
Whilst deep in slumber, it lay hidden beneath the earth's embrace.
When awakened, it would devour all souls that crossed its path.
Its shell, harder than stone, defied the strikes of common arms.
It struck fear into travelling merchants and wider to neighbouring realms.
But a yellow-furred rat sensed the immense power emanating from the insect.
He halted the beetle's havoc and harnessed it for his own ends.
Overjoyed, the king named it.
He named the rat Gwaii, the royal sage, and built a shrine in his honour.
The bound beetle was a perfect source of power, so the rat stayed.
He seized the tongue monk using a new power and battled with soon Wukong upon the Yellow Wind Ridge.
The Gwaii's formidable winds failed the vast expanse of the sky.
Were it not for Bodhisattva Lingji,
tongue monk's quest for the sun,
the scriptures would have failed.
Yet, stripped of the rat's protection,
the kingdom was plunged into a state of ruin.
The once lush Yellow Wind Ridge now lies a desolate wasteland.