You
What does it matter if you become a Buddha that headband has always been on your head
Keep those eyes wide open
Watch me rip it off and break free
Sooo
When you defied the celestial court
I had to seal you beneath the mountains with my immense power
Yet after enduring punishment you embrace the dumb
uplifted good against evil and subdued
Yaukai's throughout the journey
For your contribution. I now bestow upon you the title of victorious
victorious fighting Buddha
He defied the celestial court and the Jade Emperor imposed three ordeals
Only when the chicken finishes pecking the rice the dog laps up the flowers and the lamp burns through the key the rain will fall
My weeping Knight
In a flashed arrogance
And
You
you
bottoms up brothers one final toast before we crash the celestial palace