And so ends the last tale of Sun Wukong.
A hero who treasured his freedom above all else.
Buddhahood he attained, yes, but cumbersome he found the celestial rules,
for he yearned to come back and to revel in the simple joys with us.
Little did he know his choice to forego the life above
only fueled their mistrust.
This stone has stood for countless days on the mountain.
Since my youth,
they've said that his remains lie within it.
Unbegotten, undying, such is the nature of a stone monkey.
Though his body was broken, his spirit endures.
Into six relics he turned, and separately they escaped, choosing to stay hidden.
The stone is now a stone.
Those are the six senses of the great sage.
Yet no one has ever seen them, not in centuries.
I'm old now. Venture through all the lands I cannot.
The stone is now a stone.
Yet among you,
there might be one who is destined.
One that shall recover all his scattered relics.
And upon the return of the relics to Mount Tuaguo,
he may yet rise again.
I may ratio it now two,
punish everyone who does away with if any sin.
CRA景
가
Not a dynasty is born
to reap almost my defeat on the earth world.
To save a tribe from the hands of.»
The Burgundian, according toulturist F infected,