It's been a while, but the Immobilize spell still works like a charm.
Since you hail from Mount Huagu, it won't hurt to teach you a handy trick.
Now, here we go. Give me your hand.
There you go. Should you come across any miscreants, just point your finger at them and release this spell.
You'll be able to hold them in place while giving yourself a breather.
Sadly, mine is but a humble trick.
Its power will wear off within a few short moments.
Though it's good enough against boneheads like this one.
Anyway, just consider it an ace up your sleeve.
No! The Yaoguas these days know no manners!
Fear not. Teach them a lesson with your new spell!
A ЧЭ sensei Yaturendd and
No minute radio
Waiting
ignited
Rötting
Morning